doing in good faith and for good effort.
What do you do with that? You have to
not give up and not stop believing that
they can still do that thing that they
view as right without a a a absolute
mutation away from their known
adaptations. Not saying that their whole
training, their whole energy put into
the decision-making engine they have is
not for for not. It's not a waste, but
it need be um
capable of bearing more weight than it
was ever engineered with which to
provide. Right? Like that's what's so
tough is that we have no clue what that
engine can support. And that's sort of
the big guess is that when you unravel
that when you
ask people to see what they can do
without being in an environment in which
they've been so successful, they are
scared. And so I think that's just we
have to ask ourselves how much can we
bear to change um when you're trying to
actually do it for the better and not
just be scared and not just be
I don't know told stories that make you
never change from that pain. Um, I guess